Mitchell Lowry

UI/UX Designer

Contact

225-270-1937

mitchwayne13@gmail.com

LinkedIn

Baton Rouge, LA

Skills

Technical Adobe XD Adobe AI Marvel

Professional

Problem Solving Creative Thinking Communication Teamwork

Education

CareerFoundry

Jan 2021 - Jan 2022 UI Immersion

CareerFoundry

Nov 2020 - Dec 2020 Intro to UI Design

Profile

Goal-focused UI Designer with a newfound enjoyment for UX research, skilled in prototyping and wireframes. Currently taking a frontend development course to expand my knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JS. Successful in creating new features for all apps created for course work. Check out my Behance portfolio for examples.

Experience

Chef/Butcher

TA's Productions, Baton Rouge, LA

Sept 2017 - present

- In a brand-new commissary model, workshopped and iterated procedures for supplying goods to four restaurant locations
- Drove production increase from \$100k/week location to four locations requiring over \$400k/week
- Led team in procuring and producing product worth over \$100,000/week

Back of House Manager

Chimes Highland/Parrains, Baton Rouge, LA

July 2014 - Sept 2017

- Responsible for the training of new Managers
- Led team of 40+ while improving communication between Back of House and Front of House teams
- Increased batch cooking productivity to meet sales of \$100,000/week

Back of House Manager/Front of House Manager Another Broken Egg Cafe, Baton Rouge, LA

Fuly 2013 - Fuly 2014

- Worked with back of house and front of house vendors to negotiate services to keep food cost below 28%
- Honed customer service skills by doing 100% table visits to ensure positive guest experiences

Kitchen Manager

Parrains, Baton Rouge, LA

Sept 2009 - Fulv 2013

- Managed and scheduled a crew of up to 40 people
- Executed ordering and inventory sales of \$100,000/week
- Negotiated prices with vendors to keep food cost below 30%